SUMIT GHOSH

CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER





+917076501101



sumitghosh1994@outlook.com



Radhabazar, Nabadwip, Nadia 741302



https://youtube.com/hackwithsumit

CAREER OBJECTIVE

As a Ethical Hacker my expertise lies in implementing and maintaining robust security protocols to protect an Organization's critical assets from cyber threats. With my extensive knowledge of security technologies, I excel at identifying and mitigating security vulnerabilities to prevent data breaches and cyber-attacks..

TOOLS

- Nessus Scanning
- Metasploit
- NMAP
- SQL Map
- Burp Suite
- OWASP ZAP
- Wireshark

SKILLS

- · Android & Windows Hacking
- Linux Administration
- Manual Testing
- Desktop Support Real Life Exp

CERTIFICATIONS

DIPLOMA IN CYBERSECURITY

CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER V12

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

HIGHER SECONDARY

Nabadwip Bakultala HIgh School

SECONDARY EDUCATION

Nabadwip Bakultala HIgh School 2011

HIGHER SECONDARY

Nabadwip Bakultala HIgh School

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER V12

EC Council

APR 2023

DIPLOMA IN CYBERSECURITY

DataSpace Security FEB 2022 - MAR 2023

WORKING EXPERIENCE

SAMSUNG INDIA

Samsung Experience Consultant 2017 - 2022

AIRCEL INDIA

Customer Care Executive

Feb 2016 - July 2016

PYTHON PROGRAMMING

DataSpace Security

DataSpace Security

ANDROID PROGRAMMING

CMC Academy

FC-Council

ACHIEVEMENTS

BUG BOUNTY CHALLANGE DataSpace Academy

DATASPACE ACADEMY(BY DATASPACE SECURITY

Jr. Penetration Tester

Apr 2023 - July 2023

I hereby declare that the details and information given above are complete and true to the best of my knowledge.

Date:

Signature Place: